<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Resistor Calculator</string>
    <string name="digitTitle">Digit &amp; Multiplier Bands</string>
    <string name="toleranceTitle">Tolerance &amp; Temperature</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Explanation</string>
    <string name="title_activity_explain">Explanation</string>
    <string name="explain1">\tResistor values are an easy enough calculation once you get to
        remembering the colours. Resistors are almost always labeled with 4-6 coloured bands;
        the bands will have a large \'gap\' in the middle with 3-4 bands on one side and 1-2 bands on
        the other(three on 1 side and 1 on the other for a 4 band resistor. This gap shows us what
        the different bands represent.
        \n\n
        \tAssuming you\'re holding the resistor with the side that has more bands before the gap
        to your left; all the bands except for the one right before the gap, 1-2 or 1-3 depending on
        the number of bands, are the Digit Bands. These bands represent the actual number values.
        The final band on the left side before the gap is the multiplier band, this represents a
        power of 10 that you multiply the digit bands by to get the total number of ohms. The first
        band after the gap, (there may be only one after gap), is the Tolerance band. This band
        represents the level of error plus or minus a percent in the value of the resistor. If there
        is a 6th and final band, this band is the Tempurature band and shows the level of variance in
        resistance per degree celsius.
        \n\n
        \tFor example say we have a 4 band resistor like this one:
    </string>
    <string name="explain2" formatted="false">
        \tThe first two bands are the Digit bands, the third band would be the multiplier band, and
        that forth band after the gap, (its hard to see in a picture but in real life the gap size
        difference is there), is the tolerance band.
        \n\n
        \tSo the first two bands are Yellow(4) and Purple(7), this means our base number is 47.
        Looking at the third band we see that it is Black(0) which means we multiply our 47 by 10 to
        the power of 0, which is 1, so our final ohms value is 47. Finally we tack on our tolerance
        band Gold(5%) meaning that our resistor is a 47ohm resistor with plus or minus 5% tolerance!
    </string>

</resources>
